{"data":[{"question":"The result of the experiment was ________.","a":"satisfied","b":"satisfaction","c":"satisfactory","d":"satisfactorily","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To be + Adj.\u00a0\n+ Satisfied: pleased because something has happened in the way that you want, or because you have got what you want.\u00a0\n+ Satisfactory: something that is satisfactory seems good enough for you, or good enough for a particular situation or purpose.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"A number of ________ submitted their manuscripts under pseudonyms to conceal the fact that they were women.","a":"novel","b":"novelist","c":"novels","d":"novelists","answer":"4","explain":"\n- A number of + Plural noun.\u00a0\n- Their manuscripts: implies subject is person.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Some executives require that the secretary ________ responsible for writing all reports as well as for balancing the books.","a":"is","b":"be","c":"was","d":"been","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Require\/ suggest\/recommend ...+ that + S + Infinitive(without to) + O.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Although a doctor may be able to diagnose a problem ________, he still may not be able to find a drug to which the patient will respond.","a":"perfect","b":"perfectible","c":"perfectly","d":"perfection","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Adverb modifies Normal Verb (diagnose)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"This law is purely ________.","a":"prospect","b":"prospects","c":"prospector","d":"prospective","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Adverb can be used to modify adjective, normal verb but never modify noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The number of the days in a week ________ seven.","a":"needs","b":"are","c":"need","d":"is","answer":"4","explain":"\n-The expression\u00a0the number is followed by a singular verb while the expression a number is followed by a plural verb.\n\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Although the red cross accepts blood from most donors, the nurses will not ________ you give blood if you have just had a cold.","a":"let","b":"leave","c":"want","d":"need","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Let somebody do sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"Most comets have two kinds of tails, one made up of dust, ________ made up of electrically charged particles called plasma.","a":"one another","b":"the other","c":"other ones","d":"each other","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The other: used to refer to the second of two people or things, which is not the one you already have or the one you have already mentioned.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"By 1820, there were over sixty steamboats on the Mississippi river, ________ were quite luxurious.","a":"many of them","b":"which many","c":"many of which","d":"many that","answer":"3","explain":"\n- If a preposition is used with the relative pronoun, this preposition can either precede the pronoun or follow the verb.\u00a0\n- Which= a part of sixty steamboats on the Mississippi river.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"},{"question":"The native people of the Americans are called Indians because when Columbus landed in the Bahamas in 1492, he thought that he ________ The east Indies.","a":"has reached","b":"has been reached","c":"had been reached","d":"had reached","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past Perfect Tense: \n+ Expresses the idea that something occurred before another action in the past (thought) .","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"5","type":"1"}]}